[{"question": "<p> Find the range of <script type=\"math/tex\"> f(x)=2-\\sqrt{2-x} </script> </p>", "answers": [["a.", "the empty set", false], ["b.", "[\u20132, \u221e)", false], ["c.", "[2, \u221e)", false], ["d.", "(\u2013\u221e, 2]", true]]}, {"question": "<p> If A = (\u20132, 5) and B = [4,7], A \u1d17 B? </p>", "answers": [["a.", "the empty set", false], ["b.", "(\u2013\u221e, \u221e)", false], ["c.", "(\u20132, 7]", true], ["d.", "[\u20132, 7)", false], ["e.", "[4, 5)", false]]}, {"question": "<p> Find the range of <script type=\"math/tex\"> f(x)=\\frac{-1}{\\sqrt{2-x}} </script> </p>", "answers": [["a.", "the empty set", false], ["b.", "(\u2013\u221e, 0)", true], ["c.", "(0, \u221e)", false], ["d.", "(\u20132, \u221e)", false], ["e.", "(2, \u221e)", false]]}, {"question": "<p> If <script type=\"math/tex\"> f(t)=t^2+t </script> , find <script type=\"math/tex\"> \\frac{f(t+h)-f(t)}{h} </script> . </p>", "answers": [["a.", "2t + h + 1", true], ["b.", "2t + 1", false], ["c.", "2t", false], ["d.", "1", false], ["e.", "undefined", false]]}, {"question": "<p> If <script type=\"math/tex\"> f(x)=3x+2 </script> and <script type=\"math/tex\"> g(x)=x-4 </script> , <script type=\"math/tex\"> \\frac{f}{g}(4) </script> is: </p>", "answers": [["a.", "undefined", true], ["b.", "0", false], ["c.", "14", false], ["d.", "(3, 2, 4)", false], ["e.", "none of these", false]]}, {"question": "<p> What is the domain of <script type=\"math/tex\"> f(x)=\\frac{\\sqrt{x-5}}{\\sqrt{x}} </script> ? </p>", "answers": [["a.", "(0, 5)", false], ["b.", "[0, 5]", false], ["c.", "[5, \u221e)", true], ["d.", "[0, 5)", false], ["e.", "[5, 0)", false]]}, {"question": "<p> Given the function <script type=\"math/tex\"> g(x)=(x-1)^2 </script> , find the average rate of change on the interval [\u22121, 2]. <br/> </p>", "answers": [["a.", "-2", false], ["b.", "-1", true], ["c.", "1", false], ["d.", "2", false], ["e.", "None of the above", false]]}, {"question": "<p> Find the range of <script type=\"math/tex\"> f(x)=-\\sqrt{2-x} </script> </p>", "answers": [["a.", "the empty set", false], ["b.", "(\u2013\u221e, 0]", true], ["c.", "[0, \u221e)", false], ["d.", "[\u20132, \u221e)", false], ["e.", "[2, \u221e)", false]]}, {"question": "<p> If <script type=\"math/tex\"> f(x)=2x+1 </script> , what is the domain? </p>", "answers": [["a.", "(2, 1]", false], ["b.", "(1, 2)", false], ["c.", "[\u2013\u221e,\u221e]", false], ["d.", "(\u2013\u221e,\u221e)", true], ["e.", "(\u221e,\u2013\u221e)", false]]}, {"question": "<p> If <script type=\"math/tex\"> f(t)=t^2+t </script> , find the average rate of change on the interval [\u22121, 2]. </p>", "answers": [["a.", "-3/5", false], ["b.", "3/5", false], ["c.", "-2", false], ["d.", "2", true], ["e.", "undefined", false]]}, {"question": "<p> If <script type=\"math/tex\"> f(t)=t^2+t </script> , find the average rate of change on the interval [\u22121, 2]. <br/> </p>", "answers": [["a.", "-3/5"], ["b.", "3/5"], ["c.", "-2"], ["d.", "2"], ["e.", "undefined"]]}, {"question": "<p> If <script type=\"math/tex\"> f(x)=3x+2 </script> and <script type=\"math/tex\"> g(x)=x-4 </script> , <script type=\"math/tex\"> \\frac{f}{g}(4) </script> is: </p>", "answers": [["a.", "undefined"], ["b.", "0"], ["c.", "14"], ["d.", "(3, 2, 4)"], ["e.", "none of these"]]}, {"question": "<p> Find the range of <script type=\"math/tex\"> f(x)=-\\sqrt{2-x} </script> </p>", "answers": [["a.", "the empty set"], ["b.", "(\u2013\u221e, 0]"], ["c.", "[0, \u221e)"], ["d.", "[\u20132, \u221e)"], ["e.", "[2, \u221e)"]]}, {"question": "<p> If <script type=\"math/tex\"> f(x)=2x+1 </script> , what is the domain? </p>", "answers": [["a.", "(2, 1]"], ["b.", "(1, 2)"], ["c.", "[\u2013\u221e,\u221e]"], ["d.", "(\u2013\u221e,\u221e)"], ["e.", "(\u221e,\u2013\u221e)"]]}, {"question": "<p> What is the domain of <script type=\"math/tex\"> f(x) = \\frac{\\sqrt{x \u2013 5}}{\\sqrt{x}} </script> ? </p>", "answers": [["a.", "(0, 5)"], ["b.", "[0, 5]"], ["c.", "[5, \u221e)"], ["d.", "[0, 5)"], ["e.", "[5, 0)"]]}, {"question": "<p id=\"yui_3_17_2_1_1714047602961_245\"> If f(x) = 3x \u2013 5, what is the inverse of f? </p>", "answers": [["a.", "-3x + 5", false], ["b.", "5x \u2013 3", false], ["c.", "x/3 + 5/3", true], ["d.", "x/3 \u2013 5/3", false], ["e.", "None of these", false]]}, {"question": "<p> Let f(x) = \u2013 x <sup> 2 </sup> \u2013 4, x &lt; 0. What is f <sup> -1 </sup> ? <br/> </p>", "answers": [["a.", "\u2013\u221a(\u2013x \u2013 4)", false], ["b.", "\u2013\u221a(\u2013x \u2013 4), x < \u2013 4", true], ["c.", "\u221a(x + 4)", false], ["d.", "\u2013\u221a(\u2013x \u2013 4), x > \u2013 4", false], ["e.", "None of these", false]]}, {"question": "<p> Let f(x) = x <sup> 2 </sup> \u2013 4, x &lt; 0. What is f <sup> -1 </sup> ? </p>", "answers": [["a.", "-\u221a(x \u2013 4)", false], ["b.", "-\u221a(x \u2013 4), x > 4", false], ["c.", "-\u221a(x + 4)", false], ["d.", "-\u221a(x + 4), x >-4", true], ["e.", "None of these", false]]}, {"question": "<p> If f(x) = 2x + 3, and g(x) = x <sup> 2 </sup> + x, what is f \u25cb g? <br/> </p>", "answers": [["a.", "4x2 + 14x + 12", false], ["b.", "4x2 + 12x + 9", false], ["c.", "x2 + 3x + 3", false], ["d.", "2x2 + 2x + 3", true], ["e.", "None of these", false]]}, {"question": "<p> If f(x) = 1 / (3x \u2013 5), what is the inverse of f? <br/> </p>", "answers": [["a.", "1 / (3x + 5)", false], ["b.", "1 / (3x \u2013 5)", false], ["c.", "(1/3).(1/x \u2013 5)", false], ["d.", "(1/3).(1/x + 5)", true], ["e.", "None of these", false]]}, {"question": "<p> If f(x) = 2x + 3 and g(x) = x \u2013 5, what is g \u25cb f? <br/> </p>", "answers": [["a.", "2x + 1", false], ["b.", "2x + 2", false], ["c.", "2x - 1", false], ["d.", "2x - 2", true], ["e.", "None of these", false]]}, {"question": "<p> If f(x) = 2x + 3, and g(x) = x <sup> 2 </sup> + x, what is g \u25cb f? </p>", "answers": [["a.", "4x2 + 14x + 12", true], ["b.", "4x2 + 12x + 9", false], ["c.", "x2 + 3x + 3", false], ["d.", "2x2 +2x +3", false], ["e.", "None of these", false]]}, {"question": "<p> For f(x) = \u221a(x + 5) + 2, what is the domain of f <sup> -1 </sup> ? </p>", "answers": [["a.", "(-\u221e, \u221e)", false], ["b.", "(0, \u221e)", false], ["c.", "(-\u221e, 0)", false], ["d.", "[2, \u221e)", true], ["e.", "None of these", false]]}, {"question": "<p> If f(x) = 2x + 3 and g(x) = x \u2013 5, what is f\u25cbg? </p>", "answers": [["a.", "2x - 5", false], ["b.", "2x \u2013 7", true], ["c.", "2x \u2013 10", false], ["d.", "2x - 15", false], ["e.", "None of these", false]]}, {"question": "<p> For f(x) = \u2013\u221a(x \u2013 5) \u2013 2, what is the domain of f <sup> -1 </sup> ? <br/> </p>", "answers": [["a.", "(\u2013\u221e, 2]", false], ["b.", "[2, \u221e)", false], ["c.", "(\u2013\u221e, \u20132]", true], ["d.", "[\u20132, \u221e)", false], ["e.", "None of these", false]]}, {"question": "<p> What are the x-intercepts of f(x) = x <sup> 2 </sup> \u2013 6? </p>", "answers": [["a.", "{6, -6}", false], ["b.", "(0, -6)", false], ["c.", "(6, 0) and (-6, 0)", false], ["d.", "(\u221a6, 0) and (-\u221a6, 0)", true], ["e.", "There are no intercepts", false]]}, {"question": "<p> What is the equation of a line through (-1, 4) and (-2, 7)? </p>", "answers": [["a.", "y = 3x + 1", false], ["b.", "y = -3x + 1", true], ["c.", "y = -3x + 7", false], ["d.", "y = 3x + 7", false], ["e.", "None of these", false]]}, {"question": "<p> An equation for a line perpendicular to p(t) = 3t + 4 and passing through the point (3, 1) is: <br/> </p>", "answers": [["a.", "y = (1/3)x + 1", false], ["b.", "y = (-1/3)x + 1", false], ["c.", "y = (1/3)x + 2", false], ["d.", "y = (-1/3)x + 2", true], ["e.", "None of these", false]]}, {"question": "<p> f(x) is a quadratic function with vertex (1, \u22122), opens up. <br/> </p>", "answers": [["a.", "X2 \u2013 2x \u2013 1", true], ["b.", "X2 \u2013 2x + 1", false], ["c.", "X2 + 2x \u2013 1", false], ["d.", "X2 + 2x + 1", false], ["e.", "None of these", false]]}, {"question": "<p> Find the value of x if a linear function goes through the following points and has the following slope: (x, 2), (\u22124, 6), m = 3. <br/> </p>", "answers": [["a.", "3/16", false], ["b.", "-3/16", false], ["c.", "-16/3", true], ["d.", "16/3", false], ["e.", "None of these", false]]}, {"question": "<p> What the equation of the line passing through (1, 4) and parallel to y = 2x + 1? </p>", "answers": [["a.", "y = 2x + 2", true], ["b.", "y = 2x + 1", false], ["c.", "y = 2x", false], ["d.", "No such line exists.", false], ["e.", "None of these.", false]]}, {"question": "<p> What is the vertex of f(x) = 3(x \u2013 2) <sup> 2 </sup> + 2? </p>\n<p> <br/> </p>", "answers": [["a.", "(\u20132, \u20132)", false], ["b.", "(\u20131, \u20131)", false], ["c.", "(1, 1)", false], ["d.", "(2, 2)", true], ["e.", "None of these", false]]}, {"question": "<p> A frog jumps and takes 2 seconds to land. The path of the frog\u2019s flight is best modeled by the graph of f(x) = -x <sup> 2 </sup> + 2x. What is the maximum height of the jump? </p>", "answers": [["a.", "0", false], ["b.", "1", true], ["c.", "2", false], ["d.", "The frog jumps into outer space.", false], ["e.", "None of these.", false]]}, {"question": "<p> Where the line y = 6 meets the parabola y = x <sup> 2 </sup> + x for x &gt; 0? <br/> </p>", "answers": [["a.", "(\u20132, 6)", false], ["b.", "(\u20131, 6)", false], ["c.", "(1, 6)", false], ["d.", "(2, 6)", true], ["e.", "None of these", false]]}, {"question": "<p> What is the vertex of f(x) = x <sup> 2 </sup> + 3x + 2? </p>", "answers": [["a.", "7", false], ["b.", "(0, 2)", false], ["c.", "(-3/2, -1/4)", true], ["d.", "-3/2", false], ["e.", "None of these", false]]}]